# Jordy Hershel IGONDJO

Computer Engineer / Flutter Developer

#### **Contact**

**Address** 

Istanbul, Esenyurt, 34325

E-mail

jordy925@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/jordyhershel-ig

**www** 

www.jordyhers.com

#### **Skills**

Mobile application development

Cloud applications

Database support

API

RESTful API development

Swift

IOS

Web-based software engineering

Algorithm implementation

## Languages

Talented individual with in-depth knowledge of designing and development tools and coding languages. Desirous of the role of Computer Engineer with 3+ years of work experience in innovating software designs, testing, and coding as well as debugging programs and troubleshooting.

Expertise in coding and testing, software application development and design, including iOS and Android as well as extensive knowledge of product- oriented designs and data structures. Curious Learner having abilities to solve complex issues.

Experience with various frameworks React-Native, Hooks, Flutter - Dart, Firebase, API, RESTful API - C++, Integrated testing - Cloud Functions - Javascript. Worked on different projects related to AR and VR using Vuforia and Unity.

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

### **Work History**

2020-08 -Current

## Flutter Mobile Application Developer

DNC Studyo, Istanbul, Turkey

- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions
- Managed on-site evaluations, internal audits and customer surveys
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships
- Actively listened to customers' requests, confirming full understanding before addressing concerns
- Created Reusable and Maintainable codes
- Integrated automated testing and conducted team meetings
- Review over 5,000 lines of codes and supported open source projects

2020-07 *-* 2020-09

## **Junior React Native Developer**

Yeni Egitim Sistemi, Istanbul, Turkey

- Write, modify, integrate and test software code
- Maintain existing computer programs by making modifications as required
- Lead and co-ordinate teams of computer programmers
- Conducted researches and evaluated variety of software products
- Write, modify, integrate and test software code for e-commerce, Internet and mobile applications
- Assist in development of logical and physical specifications
- Ay research and evaluate variety of interactive media

English

French

Turkish

Spanish

Chinese

software products.

#### 2019-10 -2020-07

## **English Language Teacher**

English Time, Istanbul

- Develop curriculum and prepare teaching materials and outlines for courses
- Prepare, administer and mark tests and papers to evaluate students' progress
- Advise students on program curricula and career decisions
- Provide individualized tutorial or remedial instruction to students who require it
- Serve on committees concerned with matters such as budgets, curriculum revision, and course and diploma requirements.

### 2018-07 -2019-07

## Language Consultant

Turkish-American Association Language School, Istanbul, Turkey

 Teach students using systematic plan of lectures, demonstrations, discussion groups, laboratory work, shop sessions, seminars, case studies, field assignments and independent or group projects

### 2017-10 -2018-01

## **English Teacher**

Turkish American Association, Istanbul, Turkey

- Prepare subject material for presentation to students according to an approved curriculum
- Each students using systematic plan of lectures, discussions, audio-visual presentations, and laboratory, shop and field studies
- Assign and correct homework
- Prepare, administer and correct tests
- Valuate progress, determine individual needs of students and discuss results with parents and school officials
- Participate in staff meetings, educational conferences and teacher training workshops
- Teach and evaluate students through distance or online courses

#### **Education**

#### 2022-02 -Current

# **Master of Science: Computer Science And Programming**

IU International University of Applied Science - Germany

2017-09 - **Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering** 

# **Additional Information**

Awards and honours